Do you have a lot of friends?
Not a lot, but I have a few
very close friends.
I think it is better to have one
reliable friend than a thousand fair-weather friends.
Although it's not easy to meet someone you
have a lot in common with, I think
I manage to do it.
How often do you see your friends?
As often as I can.
We enjoy each other's company, so we see
each other almost daily.
What's more, we live very close to each
other, so it's easy for us to meet
up.
Is there anything special about your friends?
Oh, that's an interesting question.
I guess there are a lot of things.
For instance, my best friend can draw unbelievable
art, good enough to sell.
And my other friend is really keen on
cooking.
But most importantly, they are people who are
near and dear to my heart.
For how long do you know them?
I've known my friends since my childhood.
We've been through thick and thin together.
Probably that's why we're so close now.